He carried our sins on that rugged tree
To win our pardon and our victory
In jars of clay we carry the news
Christ is risen, grace has broken through
No condemnation now is ours to dread
By Your Word the faintest soul is fed
We have believed and so we loudly speak
The name of Jesus strength unto the weak
We do not hope in what is seen
But cling to Christ our certainty
The weight of glory yet to come
It's the song of heaven now begun
A new life we live by His mighty hand
Through every grief to the promised land
The Spirit's here, He knows our needs
And from His throne our Savior intercedes
We do not hope in what is seen
But cling to Christ our certainty
The weight of glory yet to come
It's the song of heaven now begun
Beyond the reach of mortal sight
Yet clearer still than brightest light
In every trial and every fall
The hope of glory outweighs them all
We do not hope in what is seen
But cling to Christ our certainty
The weight of glory yet to come
It's the song of heaven now begun
We do not hope in what is seen
But cling to Christ our certainty
The weight of glory yet to come
It's the song of heaven now begun